(Raj:)You don't have to,
you should want to.
(Leonard:)Oh, great,
there's Mandy.
(Howard:)Why are marine biologists
always so cute?
(Penny:)I don't know,
(Raj:)but I'd like to get lost
in her Bermuda Triangle.
(Leonard:)That's not helpful.
(Howard:)Then I won't say
(Howard:)I'd like to cover three-quarters
of her surface area.
(Leonard:)Are we done?
(Raj:)Not yet, this is fun.
(Raj:)Ooh, I know.
(Raj:)I'd let her free my willy.
(Raj:)Where you going?
(Leonard:)I'm gonna ask her if she'd
be willing to talk to Penny,
(Leonard:)tell her she has nothing
to worry about.
(Howard:)Leonard, wait.
What?
(Howard:)I'd like to SpongeBob
her SquarePants.
Now we are done. (chuckles)
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Mandy:)Oh, hi, Leonard. What's up?
(Leonard:)Uh, do you mind
if I sit?
(Sheldon:)Sure.
(Leonard:)So, um, I've been
thinking a lot
(Leonard:)about you and me and...
the boat.
(Mandy:)What about it?
(Penny:)You know...
(Leonard:)what we did,
when we were drunk.
(Mandy:)Oh, no,
did I sleep with you, too?